[
    {
        "Question": "How does idev work?",
        "Answer Given": "\ncmd-line\nc123-456",
        "Score": 0.13076485693454742,
        "Actual Answer": "submits a batch job that creates a copy of the batch environment"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does idev do?",
        "Answer Given": "\ncmd-line\nc123-456",
        "Score": 0.12804289162158966,
        "Actual Answer": "creates and interactive development environment from the user's login window"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the terminal command for idev?",
        "Answer Given": "\nc123-456",
        "Score": 0.14913605153560638,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the command for idev?",
        "Answer Given": "ibrun",
        "Score": 0.1548057347536087,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How much time will the system report the job status?",
        "Answer Given": "every 4 seconds",
        "Score": 0.5342329144477844,
        "Actual Answer": "every 4 seconds"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What happens on the first time launching idev?",
        "Answer Given": "\nc123-456",
        "Score": 0.09350058436393738,
        "Actual Answer": "idev will prompt you for the project name and then save your selection as the default interactive account"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you start an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "\nc123-456",
        "Score": 0.10930802673101425,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do launch an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "\ncmd-line\nc123-456",
        "Score": 0.1010497435927391,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which command launces an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "\nc123-456",
        "Score": 0.12157174944877625,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does -m do with idev",
        "Answer Given": "sets time in minutes",
        "Score": 0.29325470328330994,
        "Actual Answer": "sets time in minutes"
    }
]
